

ABOUT ME

I am a passionate web developer with 6 years of experience building virtual platforms for organizations at a professional level. I am comfortable using the following programming languages; HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP. I am creative and detail-oriented in designing platforms that are functional and user-friendly.

LINKS

- https://github.com/darjosh
- https://linkedin.com/in/joshua-segun-web
- https://codepen.io/sowotogbe/
- https://www.uniquediadem.com
- https://www.youtube.com/channel/ UCe1SclV5xq6PdeIWEuECbiw

SKILLS

Wordpress:	
AWS:	
Bootstrap:	
PHP/MYSQL:	
Graphic Design:	
Web Develop:	
HTML/HTML5:	
CSS/CSS3/SASS:	
Javascript/JSDOM:	
Git/Github·	

OWOTOGBE JOSHUA

Full stack Developer & Front-end Developer

Phone: +2348134691588 Email: owotogbesegunjoshua@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER AT ULTRA SIGHT INFOTECH (2019 – NOW)

- Pulled from PHP, SQL, JavaScript and other back-end library knowledge to bolster programming resources.
- Collaborated with graphic design personnel to integrate images as basic site components.
- Oversaw back-end development using PHP to maintain website integrity, security and efficiency.
- Converted graphic designs to usable web images using Adobe Photo Shop.
- Multi-tasked across multiple functions and roles to generate project results and meet deadlines and organizational expectations.

WEB DEVELOPER AT CLASSIC INFOTECH (2015 – 2018)

- > Responsible for entire web design process, from coding right through to rolling out of website and interpreting client's requirement.
- Registering web domain names and organizing their hosting
- > Testing websites to ensure they are working properly
- Taking projects from concept to finished product on my own
- Proof reading content to find any spelling or grammatical error
- Helped the team stick to specific standards in developing web pages under company guidelines

WEB DEVELOPER AT CALEB II (2014 – 2015)

- Assembled and addressed technical and design requirements, integrating user-facing and front-end elements to maintain web presence effectiveness.
- ➤ Tested site compatibility across multiple browsers and devices, uncovering and debugging issues and addressing inconsistencies.
- > Wrote clean HTML and CSS code, integrating design, extensions and third-party apps according to web development plans.
- Identified and resolved website performance flags to optimize speed.
- Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.
 Developed designs to meet specific requirements such as quick-loading sites with particular layouts

EDUCATION

ACHIEVERS UNIVERSITY (2018 – 2019) ODUDUWWA UNIVERSITY (2011 – 2015)

M. Sc. Computer Science

B. Sc. Computer Science